

Profile



Romina Ghaderi



rominaa.ghaderi94@ gmail.com



+46700182173



Brunskogsbacken 70 12371 FARSTA



linkedin.com/in/rominaghaderi-8b6074232



github.com/romigh94



portfolio-romigh94.vercel. app

Languages

Swedish (Native)



English



Hobbies

- Hang out with friends and family
- Big interest for Web development and Webdesign

Romina Ghaderi

Frontend developer

About me

I am a newly graduated Frontend developer with big ambitions. I have experience in React, Vue and Node.js etc. I find it easy to understand new technology, because I am a fast learner. I am also described by others as a girl with great commitment to her work and someone who spreads positive energy.

Education

Frontend development

Jensen yrkeshögskola, Kista

During my studies as a frontend developer, I have learned how to create user-friendly websites and applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, frameworks like React, Next.js, Vue.js and Bootstrap. I also learned to work with Nodejs and to create databases with MongoDB.

Allmän kurs

2016 - 2017

Södertörns folkhögskola, Solna

High school degree

Work experience

Frontend developer

apr 2023 - jun 2023

Les creatives, Stockholm

During this period, I have participated in projects and done minor tasks. I have worked with Vue.js, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Node.js and MongoDB.

Frontend developer

nov 2022 - feb 2023

Webbfabriken, Stockholm

During this period, I have developed a couple of applications, with HTML, Node.js and frameworks such as Next.js and Bootstrap. Also worked with Figma, CSS and Sass.

Assistant nurse

2020 - 2021

Vardaga, Stockholm

Worked and took care of elderly people.

Assistant nurse

2018 - 2020

Attendo, Stockholm

Worked and took care of elderly people.

References

References will be provided after request